So here is an example problem to solve.
Now, none of the mailbox, run of the routers, none of the post office offices know exactly
where the thing is going and they don't transport it to the final destination.
All they do is they transport it to the future, to a further down destination.
But what if they get it wrong?
What if one, this is like Michigan, this is Chicago, this is Dallas, and what if Michigan
thinks sending to Chicago is a good idea, Chicago thinks sending to Dallas is a good
idea, and then Dallas thinks sending to Michigan is a good idea?
Well, then Michigan's going to get it again and send it back to Chicago.
And so then what you end up with is this situation where your packet, your data, is in a loop.
Right?
This wouldn't be good for the post office and it's not good for the internet.
So you have to say, how do we solve this problem when something's wrong?
Right?
It's, you wish it were perfect, but it's not.
And so this is the kind of research question as to how to solve this kind of problem.
And we'll talk more about this in a bit when we get into a little more technical detail.
But I just wanted to sort of say, that's the kind of research and engineering that took
literally 20 years and four different versions of the ARPANET to get right.